(Bernadette:)Guys, sorry I'm late.
I have amazing news.
(Sheldon:)Bernadette, before you
change the subject,
(Sheldon:)does anyone have any
final comments on
(Sheldon:)Leonard's faulty
digestive system?
(Leonard:)So, what's your news,
Bernadette?
(Bernadette:)The thesis committee accepted
my doctoral dissertation.
I'm getting my PhD!
(Penny:)Wow!
Oh, congratulations.
(Penny:)Wow, so that means you're a
doctor, you're a doctor,
(Penny:)you're a doctor,
you're a doctor,
(Penny:)and Howard,
you know a lot of doctors.
(Howard:)Congratulations, honey.
(Bernadette:)Thank you.
(Leonard:)So, Howard, tell us,
how's it feel knowing
(Leonard:)that when you two get married,
(Leonard:)you'll be referred to
as Mr. and Dr. Wolowitz?
(Sheldon:)Unless he takes Bernadette's
last name.
(Sheldon:)And considering
her advanced status,
(Sheldon:)that could open
some doors for him.
(Howard:)Please, this isn't about me.
I'm proud of you.
(Bernadette:)Well, you'll be
really be proud of this.
(Bernadette:)I was headhunted by a big
pharmaceutical company.
(Bernadette:)They're gonna pay me
a buttload of money!
(Howard:)What?
(Leonard:)Bernadette, that's great.
(Leonard:)Howard, do you make a buttload?
(Howard:)Better than what you've
got a buttload of.
(Leonard:)Hey, if I roll down the windows
in the car, everything's peachy.
(Leonard:)If you do it,
you're still not a doctor.
(Penny:)Yeah, just a heads-up
on the car window deal.
(Penny:)It helps, but everything is
not "peachy."